(Sheldon:)Am I correct in assuming
that your attempt...
(Sheldon:)...to be accepted by Penny's peers
is based on your desire to ensure...
(Sheldon:)...your continuing mating privileges
with her?
(Leonard:)Well, I wouldn't put it
exactly that way.
(Sheldon:)How would you put it?
(Leonard:)Yeah, okay, like you said.
(Sheldon:)Huh. Seems like an awful lot of trouble
to go through for intercourse.
(Sheldon:)Don't you have access to women
who will do it for money?
(Sheldon:)By the way, another accepted usage
for the term "ho."
(Leonard:)Goodbye, Sheldon.
Now, hold on.
(Sheldon:)I believe that social convention dictate
you not arrive empty-handed.
(Sheldon:)Would you like to bring
some Cylon toast?
(Leonard:)Yeah, no, I'm trying to fit in,
not get laughed at.
(Sheldon:)What's funny about Cylon toast?